Washingtoniana Slide Collection P026 P026
Test
- Series 8: Truax Slideshows
  - Truax Slideshows (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Parades (General), undated (Item 6822)
      Parade buggy and float pulled by horses, crowd on sidewalks (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parades (General) (Pennsylvania Avenue), undated (Item 6823)
      Crowd in street (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parades (General), undated (Item 6824)
      Parade lights at night (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parades (Inaugural) (Pennsylvania Avenue), undated (Item 6825)
      President and First Lady in horse-drawn buggy, snow-covered street, crowd (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue (Pennsylvania Avenue), undated (Item 6826)
      Cars in street, streetcar, Capitol in distance (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue (Pennsylvania Avenue), undated (Item 6827)
      View from Treasury, streetcar, horse-and-buggy, Capitol in distance (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue (Pennsylvania Avenue), undated (Item 6828)
      Snow-covered street, streetcar, horse-and-buggy, Capitol in distance (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1834 (Item 6829)
      View of rolling hills, small buildings (Photographer: Unknown)
    - General Views (Washington Monument), undated (Item 6830)
      View from across Potomac of unfinished monument and surroundings (Photographer: Unknown)
    - General Views (Washington and Georgetown), 1812 (Item 6831)
      View of towns and rolling hills (Photographer: Unknown)
    - General Views (Washington, DC), 1800 (Item 6832)
      View from across Potomac, structures (Photographer: Unknown)
    - General Views (Washington, DC), undated (Item 6833)
      View of town and rolling hills (Photographer: Unknown)
    - White House (White House), 1799 (Item 6834)
      Sketch of White House and surrounding structures (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Hotels, undated (Item 6835)
    - Hotels, undated (Item 6836)
      Large building with turrets (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Hotels, undated (Item 6837)
      Sketch of mansion (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Hotels, undated (Item 6838)
    - Houses (Blaine House, 2000 Massachusetts Avenue NW), undated (Item 6839)
    - Houses (Burns Cottage), undated (Item 6840)
  - Truax Slideshows (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Houses (Burns Cottage), undated (Item 6841)
    - Houses (Burns Cottage), undated (Item 6842)
    - Houses, undated (Item 6843)
      Mansion on corner (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Houses, undated (Item 6844)
    - Houses (Rock Creek Park), undated (Item 6845)
      "Rock Creek Park - Burns"; House in woods (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Houses, undated (Item 6846)
    - Houses, undated (Item 6847)
    - Building, undated (Item 6848)
      Large white building (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Treasury (Treasury Building, 1500 Pennsylvania Avenue NW), undated (Item 6849)
      Sketch of Treasury building (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Building, undated (Item 6850)
      Sketch of white mansion, people outside (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Commercial Buildings (8th Street NW at D Street NW), undated (Item 6851)
      Lansburgh and Brother department store (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Commercial Buildings, undated (Item 6852)
    - Embassies and Legations, undated (Item 6853)
      Mansion, snow-covered street (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Embassies and Legations, undated (Item 6854)
      Mansion (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Federal Triangle (Pennsylvania Avenue, National Mall), undated (Item 6855)
      View of EPA building, National Mall and surroundings from Washington Monument, snow on ground (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Fires, undated (Item 6856)
      Sketch of men cleaning, destruction of building from fire (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Fires (Old Patent Office), undated (Item 6857)
      Sketch of fire in Old Patent Office building (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Funeral Processions, undated (Item 6858)
      Soldiers marching in street, crowd on sidewalks (Photographer: Unknown)
    - General Views (Washington, DC), 1845 (Item 6859)
      Sketch of view from Geisborough (Photographer: Unknown)
    - General Views (Washington, DC), 1845 (Item 6860)
      Colored sketch of view from Geisborough (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Truax Slideshows (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - General Views, undated (Item 6861)
      Canon, buildings in background (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Agriculture Dept Bldgs, undated (Item 6862)
      Two red-brick buildings, white building to side (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Agriculture Dept Bldgs (Washington Monument), undated (Item 6863)
      View of unfinished Washington Monument and surroundings (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Agriculture Dept Bldgs, undated (Item 6864)
      Man with unicycle outside large building (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Agriculture Dept Bldgs, undated (Item 6865)
      "Tree House" (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Bridges (Potomac River), undated (Item 6866)
      Railroad bridge; "Old bridge across Potomac" (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Bridges (Potomac River), undated (Item 6867)
      Bridge across river (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Bridges (Potomac River), undated (Item 6868)
      Bridge across river, horse-and-buggies crossing (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Center Market (7th Street NW at Pennsylvania Avenue NW), undated (Item 6869)
      People and plants outside building (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Center Market (7th Street NW at Pennsylvania Avenue NW), undated (Item 6870)
      People looking at produce and plants sold from carts (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Churches (1313 New York Avenue NW), undated (Item 6871)
      New York Avenue Presbyterian Church and surrounding buildings (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Churches (Lafayette Square), undated (Item 6872)
      St. John's Church, White House in background (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Churches (National Cathedral), undated (Item 6873)
      View of National Cathedral from field (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Churches (National Cathedral), undated (Item 6874)
      National Cathedral and adjacent buildings (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Civil War (Tenleytown), Ca. 1861-1865 (Item 6875)
      Camp Tennelly; Tents on field (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Civil War, Ca. 1861-1865 (Item 6876)
      Lincoln with soldiers operating canon, farmland in distance (Photographer: Unknown)
    - White House (White House), undated (Item 6877)
    - White House (White House), 1807 (Item 6878)
    - White House (White House), undated (Item 6879)
      Sketch of "The President's House in Washington, lately taken and destroyed by the British Army" (Photographer: Unknown)
    - White House (White House), undated (Item 6880)
      Sketch of White House from Potomac River (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Truax Slideshows (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - White House (White House), 1820 (Item 6881)
      "Front view of the President's House" (Photographer: Unknown)
    - White House (White House), undated (Item 6882)
      Sketch of White House, people in fine clothing on lawn (Photographer: Unknown)
    - White House (White House), undated (Item 6883)
      White House and driveway (Photographer: Unknown)
    - White House (White House), undated (Item 6884)
      View from above of White House and West Wing, grounds (Photographer: Unknown)
    - World War I (Lincoln Memorial), Ca. 1914-1918 (Item 6885)
      View of large building from Washington Monument, Lincoln Memorial and Potomac in distance (Photographer: Unknown)
    - World War I (Potomac River), Ca. 1914-1918 (Item 6886)
      Bright lights over river (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Houses, undated (Item 6887)
      Castle and grounds (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Houses (Potomac River), undated (Item 6888)
      House on river (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Houses (Arlington House, Fort Myer, VA), undated (Item 6889)
    - Houses, undated (Item 6890)
    - Houses, undated (Item 6891)
    - Houses, undated (Item 6892)
      Small buildings in front of larger building (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Houses (Old Stone House, 3051 M Street NW), undated (Item 6893)
      Old Stone House from street (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Houses, undated (Item 6894)
      Mansion with turret (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Houses, undated (Item 6895)
    - Houses, undated (Item 6896)
      Mansion with people on roof and porch (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Houses, undated (Item 6897)
      Woman getting water from well outside building (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Houses, undated (Item 6898)
    - Houses, undated (Item 6899)
      Mansion, people on street (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Houses, undated (Item 6900)
      "George Washington's House in Washington (Built by him in 1792)" (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Truax Slideshows (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Indians, undated (Item 6901)
      Sketch of three Native Americans, baby and dog across Potomac from city (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jones Point (Jones Point, Alexandria, VA), undated (Item 6902)
      Lighthouse/structure on beach (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Jones Point (Jones Point, Alexandria, VA), undated (Item 6903)
      South corner boundary stone for District of Columbia in opening in seawall (Photographer: Unknown)